It has begun! Ano channel! Applause!
Thank you! It's started!
It's been a while!
Long time no see! Hello!
We want you to put it down well! Thank you very much!
What? It's been 2 years ago! I got it!
I wanted to share with you that the lyrics of your song are wonderful.
I wanted to tell you that the lyrics are wonderful!
Yes, I did.
And now, you've released a lot of songs from her, haven't you?
What do you think? What do you mean by "another one"?
I've been posting it on my YouTube page...
I'm kind of embarrassed to be praised.
But it's really nice.
Not giving a smiley face... that's really nice.
Oh!
Thank you.
Yes.
That slide where he expresses his opinion on the product while riding the bass guitar was perfect.
I'm not a fan of hot people either.
It's true.
It's a double whammy.
I'll be back later with a much cooler presentation.
Now, Anochan, please announce the title of this project.
Yes, ma'am.
Silmon Grand Prix in the world.
Thank you very much.
Aron-chan is a big fan of those who die.
Last time, we decided on the number one cup of soup on the market.
Do you remember that?
I remember. It was so hard.
Yes, it was. Tell me it took you a long time.
How many kinds?
Ninety kinds. Ninety kinds!
I had 90 kinds.
That's right.
That's why I'm really freaked out.
They called me Silwan today. He called me Silwan today.
It was the worst.
I remember how harsh it was.
I called you, didn't I?
I had a dream that I wanted to get a message of support.
I had the image of you doing the same thing.
I have this image of you doing the same thing about 3 times a month.
I called you to see if you already know the pain I'm going through, but you've already surpassed me.
You don't eat 90 kinds of food again? I won't say that.
I've got a great plan for you.
Today...
I'm going to let you decide who's the number one soup in the world.
We're going to let you decide who's the number one soup in the world.
That's why we've kept it small.
We've kept it small.
How many?
Ten.
Ten?
So-so, so-so, so-so.
10, compared to, say, 90.
It's true, even 10 is a lot.
I already drank some miso soup.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Oh, so you put Japan in once.
I was in Japan.
There is no Japan in this year's contest.
We have the soup of the world in the competition.
Oh, you mean like that?
Yes, that's right. Do you know what kind of world soups we have?
Mr. Tomoyam.
Oh, that's good. Do you like it?
I like it. I like the ones without the pak choi.
I don't like crunchy food.
I can only eat things that don't have it in them. I'll be honest.
And what's that Korean thing again? Like sundubu.
I like spicy food.
Do you like spicy food? Are you a lover?
I am relieved.
I was a little rough on Mr. Foody when I was in the crunchy.
I absolutely can't do crunchy.
Absolutely not.
It's in the basics.
The basics are in there.
Oh, no.
Theory is the only thing that's...you can't even struggle with this? Like this.
Also, I can't eat white stew.
There are a lot of them in the world, aren't there? The world is.
Isn't the world full of milk soup? The world.
And I can't eat vegetables in it.
I can't eat what I can't eat.
I said I like soup, but I didn't say I like the ingredients.
That's why I often refer to my favorite food as soup,
When I say "soup," people think I'm including vegetables.
That's the policy.
It's decided!
Two mouthfuls of soup!
Now, here are the world's supermarkets we've prepared for you! I wonder which one of us is the country's manufacturer?
There are so many katakana!
If it says "Bon" in bold, you'd think it's a country maker, wouldn't you?
Doesn't clam chowder taste like stew?
Well, it's close to stew.
Maybe not.
But there's a pattern where a new door is opened here.
I'd like you to see it for yourself.
And you, my dear, will be judged strictly on appearance, taste and overall image.
I'd like you to rank them according to their appearance, taste, and overall image.
I would like you to rank them accordingly.
We'll let you decide on the final top three.
Which soups shall we choose?
Minestrone
Yes, Italian minestrone.
Why first?
I like it. First? I like it. I like this nice first? I love it.
I love it.
I like it, frankly.
But sometimes there's like vegetables or beans or something in it.
And then...
I usually just drink up all the broth.
I just leave the ingredients.
I see.
I like the soup that's blended in.
But I really like the juice.
The minestrone.
Okay, then.
Minestrone, please.
Right in front of you.
The minestrone is right in front of you.
I don't know.
What do you think?
I know what minestrone is, right? And some parsley for garnish.
I don't need this.
It's soup, so...
Bon appétit!
What do you think?
What do you think? Your spoon is advancing.
Yes, yes, yes.
Tomatoes.
Tomato-based... how's that for a vegetable hater like me?
I love tomatoes.
Then this minestrone is...
Delicious!
I love it. I love it.
I love it.
The word "minestrone" means "soup with a lot of ingredients.
I think it has a lot of ingredients.
I always like to eat minestrone with soup.
I always like to eat minestrone soup, but I have the impression that it's very difficult to eat it like this.
If you don't bring a colander, it's hard to absorb the soup perfectly. The downside is that you have to bring a colander or something with you, otherwise it's hard to absorb the juice perfectly.
I think of it as "cos" already.
The ingredients are so delicious!
There is also a history of this dish. Minestrone.
No problem, there are 10 of them.
Yes, you can search for each one.
Thank you very much.
What do you think of this minestrone?
Shibuya?
Oh, roughly!
A little too many people
I have to write it down.
The atmosphere reminded me a little of a scramble crossing.
How did you get to know it?
Tentative first place!
Congratulations!
Congratulations! Now what shall we have next?
Briar bass. French briar bass, sir.
What?
You didn't see it? Is this soup?
It's only a little.
I don't know what it is.
It's a local dish from the Mediterranean coast of France, like Marseilles.
It's a soup with a lot of seafood in it.
It's a soup filled with seafood and flavored with cherry.
It's filled with detergent.
It's not soflan... and you don't put fabric softener in it.
seafood... is seafood okay?
I like seafood.
It's a fisherman's dish.
It was originally a fisherman's dish.
That's how it started.
I didn't know that.
Ah...
Yes, yes, yes.
What do you think of this soup?
The soup...
Yuck! Ugh.
It feels a little bit thirsty.
Sweet.
Oh, I see.
It's sweet, and there's a lot of seafood flavor.
Have you decided on the order?
Yes, sir.
Please!
This way.
Second place!
Yes! Why is this?
I like seafood, but the taste... I prefer seafood in soup curry.
I see... it should have a little more impact.
It tastes a little too refined for me.
It was like a soup for adults.
What do you think of this soup?
How would you describe it?
Well, I don't know...
I came to Ginza by mistake.
It's like a fisherman.
You're a bit arrogant, aren't you?
You're excited to be in Ginza, but you don't belong there.
But I feel like I don't belong here.
I feel like I don't belong here.
Now let's go to the next soup!
Uh, Tomoyamo cans.
Wow!
You're from Thailand?
Yes, it is.
I love it.
What's this?
This is not the one I know.
It's not the one I know.
Really?
I like the Tom Yum Kung flavor of ramen noodles.
That color?
You're kidding?
Okay, then. Okay, then.
It's absolutely gorgeous.
Speak up.
Yes, it is.
Because it's full of ingredients and it's one of the three best soups in the world.
Shrimp, I love shrimp.
I'm glad.
Then, please enjoy the soup with whatever ingredients you like.
What do you think?
Yes, I like it. Then, the soup. What do you think? Yeah.
Okay, sticker.
Oh, come on, follow him.
Yes, sir.
What do you think?
Delicious.
Here it comes! It's great!
What do you like about it?
It tastes amazing! What do you like about it? Do you have a favorite part? Taste
I'm hooked.
It's just that it kind of
The smell.
What do you think?
Is it the pak choi after all?
Is it in there?
I took out the maximum.
Maximum.
I knew I detected a little bit of crunchiness.
I thought my Pakuchi antenna had caught it.
The ingredients are shrimp mushrooms, lemongrass, a little bit of pak choi, and fish sauce.
It has a strong pungent taste.
The spiciness is so strong that it doesn't really matter what you do with it.
It drowns out everything else.
I don't care about the pak choi.
I see
But since you like Tom Yum!
So here's a Tom Yum quiz!
What? What's that? I don't want it. What? What's that? I don't need it.
Tom means boil, and Yamu means mix.
What's "kun"?
Don't you eat it?
I see... No!
Let me give you a hint.
It's what Ano-chan loves.
What is it?
The penis?
What?
Was it in there?
Is it in there?
Yes!
It's one of the things in there.
And this guy...
I thought, "That's what I'm talking about.
Shrimp? That's right.
Shrimp is a "kun"?
That's right.
That's why I was so happy to see you attracted her favorite food, Tom Yum.
I remember now.
Please remember.
Let's ask them to rank them.
Please, let's ask them to rank them.
Let's have them rank them.
Wow, we're in first place.
Why number one? I thought it was delicious.
Because it's spicy.
I think the last time I tried white, spicy food was usually at the top of the list.
I see... you like it and I like it.
Only a little crunchy, but other than that, perfect!
Wow, it's wonderful!
It was delicious!
It was good.
So, how would you describe this Tom Yum?
A ding dong.
Yes?
I'm wearing a key chain of "Chin-tama-kun", I'm wearing a key chain of Kachintama-kun,
I thought it would be more cute and I accepted it, but it was just the way it was.
I thought it would be very cute, but it's just the way it is.
It's because I already love it.
So that's how it is, you love it so much!
That's why I love it so much.
Thank you very much.
Let's move on to the next soup.
Spanish gazpacho!
I don't know this one very well.
What? What's this?
Oh, yeah.
It looks like it could be soup.
Oh, sure.
I'm not sure I like it as much as it looks. What is it about these brightly colored vegetables that makes me so disgusted?
I see, for a vegetable hater, something like minestrone was still blended in, but as a garnish. It's bare.
It is a typical Spanish soup, a cold soup made of raw vegetables and bread, etc., blended in a blender.
Oh, it's cold.
Yes, I guess it's cold.
Then the ingredients are, you know, tomatoes, cucumbers, onions, green peppers, buckets, and so on.
I can't eat more raw.
What are you really doing?
It's a little low on juice.
There it is.
Just tell me when you put it in.
I'll have the juice, then.
Here's your juice.
Delicious!
The vegetables are here.
The vegetables are in the soup, too.
But there's tomatoes in it. I love tomatoes.
No, not at all.
It tastes like a lot more than just tomatoes.
Makine!
Yes, it tastes like summer.
It tastes like summer.
That's wonderful.
Yes, it is. That's right.
It's also a food to be enjoyed in the summer!
Shepherds ate this soup to rehydrate and nourish themselves in the extreme heat.
They ate this soup to rehydrate and nourish themselves.
That's Hinomactan.
Doesn't this taste like paprika?
It seems to have a lot of it.
I often do dentistry, but I don't like the discoloration.
I'm sure many of you don't like it because it's too sharp.
Maybe that's it.
I'm sure there's a lot of things you don't like about it. Maybe that's the case.
Try it!
I don't think so.
Really?
I've never had gazbacho before.
It's my first time, too.
It looks so beautiful.
It's so bright and beautiful.
It's bright and it's got olive oil on it.
It's so bright and shiny.
It's definitely a fresh vegetable.
Hurry up and eat it!
You don't want a report?
No! It's not that kind of show.
It's not that kind of show! I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm used to it.
I beg your pardon.
I'm sorry.
I'm just enjoying the crunchy, firm, raw vegetables.
It's almost like a dressing, but more like a vegetable.
It's almost like a dressing.
Let's see if we can rank them.
Let's see if we can rank them higher or lower.
I'm sorry.
Let's move on to the next one.
Shark fin soup.
Here it is.
Have you ever had it? Have you ever had it?
Fine food? I've never had it.
Then this is my first shark fin soup.
It looks delicious, like ramen soup.
What about the aroma?
It smells like a dirty Chinese restaurant.
It's very dancy for such a high quality food.
It looks delicious.
Is that a common compliment?
I like that kind of thing.
But there's, like, a lot of hair in there.
Is that what this is?
This is scary!
What is shark fin?
I don't know.
Most people eat it mixed in with the soup.
It's delicious.
It's so good, so good, so good! It's just like the soup at Bamiyan!
I love the soup at Bamiyan.
It's a little bit like that.
It's that color.
That's right.
It tastes just like the all-you-can-eat soup at Bamiyan.
Just like that!
Actually, this is shark fin soup.
It's one of the world's top three soups.
Everyone loves it.
Shark's fin is shark's fin.
What? This?
Yes, sir.
Shark fin?
When shark fins are dried, they are put back in the soup.
I see. You mean it has the taste of shark's fin?
Actually, you can't add that much flavor to shark fins.
They just enjoy the texture of it, but the soup itself is the arm.
I don't know. But I don't think it makes much sense to use the shark's fin.
But I don't think it makes much sense to put the shark's fin in the soup.
You should put bamboo shoots in it. You should put bamboo shoots in.
Yes, bamboo shoots would make it crispier.
Here it is.
Here it is, in second place.
Yes, it went up a lot!
I like the basic taste of Chinese food, so it was pretty good.
I also like it better when it's not so thick, because it's a little thick.
I see, it comes closer to Vermya's soup.
So.
Now let's get to the next soup.
Samgyetang.
Samgyetang, please.
Looks delicious.
I'm so glad.
How about the aroma?
It smells great.
Good.
Try it.
It's good. It tastes tender.
It's a nice touch for those who are cold.
It's a little...
It's delicious, but the taste is too mild.
I like to eat sill as a staple food.
If it's too mild, I don't feel satisfied with it.
I'd like you to go over it already.
I want to cook it down more and more.
It's a typical Korean local dish
Whole young chicken with glutinous rice...
Glutinous rice, ginseng...
Natsume, etc.
Stuffed with Chinese herbs.
The soup is made with ginger and other ingredients.
That's why it's so good for you.
When you go to a barbecue restaurant, you order a soup with ginger and other ingredients, so it's really good for you.
When you go to a barbecue restaurant, you can order soup.
If it's spicy, you don't need meat, do you? No meat? I really don't like meat in soup.
Let's see how you rank. This is a rank spectacle!
Here it is!
Not ranked!
I've praised it so much, but it's not ranked!
It's delicious, but...
But it's kind of sad.
I got a lonely feeling
Sorry.
How do you feel about samgyetang?
How do you feel?
Deserted island
I feel lonely
I see the sea all around me
It's true
It's a waterway.
Floating in the water
He looks so lonely, so uneaten.
It's like he's waiting to be picked up.
We'll eat together later.
Great, let's go ashore now, all of us.
It's the SDGs.
Let's move on to the next soup. What are we going to do?
It's called "German 70%.
It's so long, isn't it?
Here we are in front of you. It's my first time, too.
The tableware is cute.
It's nice.
Dish.
Do you smell that?
It smells so good!
Ingredients: potatoes, carrots, onions, leeks, sausage, butter, consommé, water, and finally mashed potatoes.
This sounds good!
As far as the ingredients go...
This looks good! Oh, my! I'm glad to hear that, as far as the ingredients go.
Oh, please.
Hot.
Ah! Yum!
Wow, there it is! Wow, there it is!
It's so good!
Eeeeee!
I'm glad it was good.
This is so good!
What's the seasoning?
It's based on consommé, but there's butter and stuff.
And mashed potatoes at the end?
Mashed potatoes.
What's that stuck in your throat?
I have a tickle in my throat.
It tastes really good, but...
But I'm a little concerned about the thickening.
I see.
In case you're wondering, in Germany, potatoes are
In Germany, potatoes are eaten as much as rice is to the Japanese
potatoes are eaten as much as rice is eaten by the Japanese.
Potatoes
There are a lot of potatoes in this dish.
That's what I heard.
Caltofel, this is what it means to have potatoes in your food.
This is potato
Zuppe is a soup
This is cartoffel zuppe.
It means potato.
It's potato soup.
And it's really loved by the people.
There's a saying.
Let's have a look at the ground.
Ah-da-uh...
Masutten Baleel
Ellen, I'd like to go to the store. - Die Dick Can Dick Ten Calfairy.
Thank you very much.
You did a great job!
It means that Dick has captured it wonderfully!
I don't know what this means.
What does it mean? What do you mean?
What? Does it mean I'm gonna die?
There were so many of them.
Eat this and die? Eat this and die?
The literal translation is.
"The dumbest farmer picks the biggest potatoes.
It's a saying.
Even if you're smart, it doesn't mean you'll be successful.
It's like saying that you can get great success and profit without much effort
You can get great success and profit without much hardship
That's what I meant.
I hope you like it.
Please join us.
This is a little bit like this.
Here it is... second place.
The tomato-based minestrone, which was so strong, fell...
This soup is almost like a pot-au-feu, and I love pot-au-feu.
I love pot-au-feu.
I love pot-au-feu, and I love what's in it.
Carrots, sausage, potatoes...
It's very close to pot-au-feu.
So it went to the second place.
I wonder what would happen if he made his own pot-au-feu?
Well, let's move on to the next soup.
Clam chowder.
Take off the pot-au-feu.
Have you ever had a good meal?
I don't think I've ever had a stew and a clam chowder that I didn't know what it was.
I don't think I've ever eaten a stew and clam chowder without knowing what it was.
I see. Then let's face it this time.
How's your stomach?
I'm full.
Oh, here it comes!
So you're saying you're a little adverse to clam chowder in there?
Yeah, it's a stew. It's a stew, right?
It's a seafood stew. It's a seafood stew.
It looks like seafood stew. It's like.
Is it seafood?
English.
Clam, which means "mummy mussel
which means
means a soup with a lot of ingredients.
chowder
Put these together and you get clam chowder.
Come on, soup, yeah, yeah.
Okay, that's enough.
It means clam chowder, which you know.
Let's see what you got for me.
Yes, sir.
No, I'm not ranked.
I'm not very good at it. Not ranked!
I'm not very good at it.
I'm sorry, but if I were to give you an analogy for this image of soup...
It's like a boss who doesn't return your drink...
I hate it.
I'm tired of being with someone who doesn't like to be bothered by me.
I hate it when I'm the one who's pestering him.
We'll all enjoy the food. Thank you very much.
We'll keep the boss company.
Let's go to the next soup.
Sundubu jjigae.
Looks delicious.
It doesn't really need any garnish.
Bon appétit!
Here's the soup.
Mm-hm. - Mm-hm.
Mm-hm.
Yup. - Yup.
Yes. - Yes.
I don't know what's going on anymore.
I'm not sure anymore.
I gave him too much to drink. I gave him too much to drink
I don't know if it's good or not, but I don't know if it's good or not.
I don't know if it's good or not.
I don't know if it tastes like this.
It's a classic Korean dish!
If you write "sundoufu" in Chinese characters...
It's written in Chinese characters like "pure tofu".
What does it mean?
What?
I think it means "chige" or "chige" or something like that.
I see... pure tofu and chige for me.
That's right.
Chige.
It's a hot pot.
Yes.
It's the whole look of the thing.
I see.
I guess it's random.
Have you decided on a ranking?
I'm having a hard time deciding.
That's the point.
So the ranking of the spicy ones is now firmly fixed.
What was that?
Yes, I had it just now.
Okay, let's see...
Here it is! Second place!
Oh, Tom Yum, you didn't win!
He said it was so good, he won second place!
Yes, it was!
It's really good, but...
Tom Yum is a little bit like a bite, but you can't stop eating.
I see!
Now, the last dish left!
My favorite Pot-au-feu!
How's your stomach feeling?
I really want to decide after just one bite.
It's true... it's my favorite. It's true, it's my favorite food, so I can eat it!
Here it is, my favorite pot-au-feu!
Goooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!
It's huge!
This is pot-au-feu, right?
I really love pot-au-feu soup
There are so many goo...
It's nice to know that you like the soup.
I'll rank them according to their soup. I love this refreshing tea!
I like tea, not mud.
Pot-au-feu means "pot-au-feu" in Japanese.
I like tea, not mud, but pot-au-feu...
Pot-au-feu
Let's see...
It's hard to rank.
That's what I meant.
I've already eaten all of it.
Do you want to keep the ingredients?
Yes.
I'm already at the bottom of the list.
Is there such a wide range?
I don't know... but it's big... so I just know... but is there such a wide range?
It's just a sil.
Yes, that's right, Silwan in the world.
The winner, I'd like you to judge this one.
Anna, please think about it.
Who will be the winner of "Silwan in the world"?
The winner is...
I'm sorry.
There.
Here we go.
Oh, hello.
Pot-au-feu.
Pot-au-feu! Pot-au-feu!
Pot-au-feu is number one.
Wow! Even Nikkori Mark!
What is the key to pot-au-feu without the spiciness? What is the key to pot-au-feu with less spiciness?
Well, it's something very simply seasoned, yet delicious.
There was nothing in the way.
Well, it is a soup that is meant to be blended into the broth, right?
There is no cloying taste in the soup.
It is wonderful.
How would you describe your image of this pot-au-feu?
How do you live?
It's exactly the same as that message. It's still the lowest in my opinion, including the goo.
To be honest, I'm a professed fan of Syl, and Syl doesn't have any goo in it.
I've heard many words about his works, but I think this is exactly what he meant by "how to live.
So that's what it means.
What was it once? Yes!
Summing up!
Yes, thank you very much!
As a juice lover.
Once again
I never had a chance to compare them.
I'm glad I did!
So, in the end
a pot of pho that you can make at home.
came with
a sense of security.
I see.
It was delicious, but it was all
Really, everyone should eat it.
Thank you very much
We have plenty of leftover ingredients
I will take it well
See you next time
Bye bye bye